<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grover Tech</title><link>/posts/grover-tech/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/grover-tech/</guid><description>What is Grover?
Grover is like Netflix for gadgets. Instead of buying expensive tech outright, you rent it for a flexible monthly fee. They’ve got pretty much everything — phones, laptops, tablets, gaming consoles, headphones, even smart TVs. 💡 Why would you rent tech instead of buying?
Lower upfront cost – You don’t have to drop €1,000 on a laptop or console. Instead, you pay a smaller monthly fee. Flexibility – Need something for 1 month, 3 months, or longer?</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/tech.jpeg" alt="Grover tech"></p>
<p>What is Grover?</p>
<p>Grover is like Netflix for gadgets. Instead of buying expensive tech outright, you rent it for a flexible monthly fee. They’ve got pretty much everything — phones, laptops, tablets, gaming consoles, headphones, even smart TVs.
💡 Why would you rent tech instead of buying?</p>
<pre><code>Lower upfront cost – You don’t have to drop €1,000 on a laptop or console. Instead, you pay a smaller monthly fee.

Flexibility – Need something for 1 month, 3 months, or longer? You decide how long you keep it.

Always up to date – Tech moves fast. Renting means you can easily swap to the newest model when your subscription ends.

Try before you commit – Not sure if that iPad or PlayStation 5 is worth it? Rent it, test it, then decide if you want to buy.

Peace of mind – Grover includes insurance against accidental damage, so you’re covered if something happens.

Sustainable – Devices get reused and recycled instead of gathering dust in a drawer or ending up as e-waste.
</code></pre>
<p>🎮 Example Scenarios</p>
<pre><code>Want a PlayStation 5 for a few months while a new game drops? Rent it, then return it.

Need a laptop for a short project or while traveling? Rent instead of buying a second device.

Thinking about switching to a foldable phone but not sure? Rent it first.
</code></pre>
<p>👉 In short: Grover makes tech more affordable, flexible, and sustainable. You get the latest gadgets without being locked into ownership, and you only pay while you actually use them.</p>
<p>I think you’ll like renting tech with Grover.
If you start a subscription via this link, you get a 1-month free rental Voucher. Sign up with this invitation link:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.grover.com/de-en/referred/R-MZ0E7PQF">https://www.grover.com/de-en/referred/R-MZ0E7PQF</a></p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Exam Monitoring Script</title><link>/posts/exam-monitoring-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/exam-monitoring-script/</guid><description>On Friday 25 September I completed the exam and submitted the report! Managed to get 9 flags. Must admit the report writing is the hard part and don&amp;rsquo;t wait until last minute to start working on the report. Try and capture the steps and screenshots throughout the engagement. After anxiously waiting for the results I decided to modify an existing python script to monitor the exam result. As to give something back to the community I adjusted it to make use of Mailgun - to send the email.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Friday 25 September I completed the exam and submitted the report! Managed to get 9 flags. Must admit the report writing is the hard part and don&rsquo;t wait until last minute to start working on the report. Try and capture the steps and screenshots throughout the engagement.
After anxiously waiting for the results I decided to modify an existing python script to monitor the exam result.
As to give something back to the community I adjusted it to make use of Mailgun - to send the email.
It&rsquo;s deployed using GitHub Actions with a cron schedule and can also then be run manually.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/livewireza/cbbh-exam-check/blob/main/check_htb_exam.py">https://github.com/livewireza/cbbh-exam-check/blob/main/check_htb_exam.py</a></p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Creative thinking</title><link>/posts/creative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/creative/</guid><description>One will need creative thinking to tackle some of the vulnerabilties in the CBBH exam. This is especially true as you will need to be thinking about chaining as well. None of the targets would be expliotable with just running automated tools. There&amp;rsquo;s also the extra difficulty of &amp;ldquo;chaining&amp;rdquo; vulns. I found the following video nicely explain &amp;ldquo;Creative thinking&amp;rdquo; by Professor Po-Shen from the Carnegie Mellon University.
How to be a creative thinker | Carnegie Mellon University Po-Shen Loh</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One will need creative thinking to tackle some of the vulnerabilties in the CBBH exam. This is especially true as you will need to be thinking about chaining as well.
None of the targets would be expliotable with just running automated tools. There&rsquo;s also the extra difficulty of &ldquo;chaining&rdquo; vulns.
I found the following video nicely explain &ldquo;Creative thinking&rdquo; by Professor Po-Shen from the Carnegie Mellon University.</p>
<p>How to be a creative thinker | Carnegie Mellon University Po-Shen Loh</p>

<div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
  <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JpYA7WXkHyI" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video"></iframe>
</div>

]]></content></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>The blog&amp;rsquo;s aim is to cover everything related to Hackthebox&amp;rsquo;s CBBH path. Will try and share some tips and nuggets along the way.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The blog&rsquo;s aim is to cover everything related to Hackthebox&rsquo;s CBBH path.
Will try and share some tips and nuggets along the way.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>CBBH Tips</title><link>/posts/post1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/post1/</guid><description>I feel there&amp;rsquo;s some missing pieces to HTB CBBH training. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong the modules are good but in my opinion doesnt prepare you fully for the exam. I had to found out there&amp;rsquo;s some golden nugget modules available that will be an advantage to complete.
Take a look at the learning process module:
https://sleeperhacks.gitbook.io/htb-academy-walkthroughs/other-modules/learning-process
The other module that was also mentioned by someone else, unfortunately I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recall but seems to be also valuable for learning black box testing.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I feel there&rsquo;s some missing pieces to HTB CBBH training. Don&rsquo;t get me wrong the modules are good but in my opinion doesnt prepare you fully for the exam. I had to found out there&rsquo;s some golden nugget modules available that will be an advantage to complete.</p>
<p>Take a look at the learning process module:</p>
<p><a href="https://sleeperhacks.gitbook.io/htb-academy-walkthroughs/other-modules/learning-process">https://sleeperhacks.gitbook.io/htb-academy-walkthroughs/other-modules/learning-process</a></p>
<p>The other module that was also mentioned by someone else, unfortunately I couldn&rsquo;t recall but seems to be also valuable for learning black box testing.</p>
<p>External testing section of the Attacking Enterprise Networks.</p>
<p>The other one is the Documentation and Reporting module. ( not part of the CBBH path currently )</p>
<p>CBBH covers a broad range of web vulns but mastering the most commonly exploited attacks vectors are crucial.</p>
<p>Critical to understand how to exploit black box vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>Black box = PortSwigger Academy</p>
<p>And note all injections could be blind. I will add htb module links soon.</p>
<p><a href="https://academy.hackthebox.com/course/preview/documentation--reporting">https://academy.hackthebox.com/course/preview/documentation--reporting</a></p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>